It's been a while.
久しぶりです
What happened?
どうしたんですか?
I came to the room.
部屋に来ちゃいました
First of all, is there a problem?
まずは問題ですか?
I had fun last time, so again...
この前楽しかったので、また...
I want to do something.
何かしたいなって
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Oh no.
やば
Is it okay?
いいの?
yes.
はい
I'd love to.
是非
picture?
え?
It's a bit messy though.
ちょっと散らかってるけど
Is it okay at all?
全 然いいんですか?
of course.
もちろん
please.
どうぞ
Sorry to bother you.
お邪魔します
please.
どうぞ
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Sorry.
すいません
Were you doing it alone?
一人でしてたんですか?
Well, that's right.
まあまあ、そうなんです
No, I'm sorry about this.
いや、これはちょっとごめんなさい
No, I'm sorry.
いや、すいません
Sorry.
すいません
I was so horny.
ムラムラしてたんです
That's right.
そうなんですよ
I'm horny and want to be attacked.
ムラムラして、攻められたい
picture?
え?
Do you want me?
私がいいの?
That's what I said.
って言ったから
yes.
はい
I want to be attacked today.
今日は攻められたい
Is it okay?
いいの?
TRUE?
本当?
picture?
え?
Seriously?
マジで?
Is it okay?
いいの?
amazing.
すごい
You look cute today too.
今日もかわいいね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
So, by any chance, did you come here to have sex with me?
じゃあ、ひょっとして レッチしにきちゃったの?
that's right.
そうです
Wow.
うわ
I want to be attacked.
攻められたいんだ
It was okay.
大丈夫だったんだね
Yeah, it was fine.
うん、大丈夫だった
Ah, it's not see-through.
あ、なんか透けてない
Haven't you clicked?
ポチってしてない?
Hands on.
手ついてて
Wow, it's about time.
うわ、そろそろ
Oh no.
やば
I can see it.
見えちゃってるよ
It's a string.
ひもじゃん
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
TRUE?
本当?
I'm afraid.
恐れちゃう
Wow, erotic.
うわ、エロー
cormorant
う
Hmm.
ーん
う ーん
Hmm.
うーん
う ーん
Hmm.
うーん
No, this is it.
の ぶらじゃん、これ
Hanging out.
のぶら
Oh no.
やば
be done.
される
I thought it would happen.
されると思ってきたんだ
Wow.
うわ
Did you do it?
やっちゃった?
Spill it away.
こ ぼしといて
Wow.
うわ
Is it okay to be this intense?
こんな激しくていいの?
Do you also like intense things?
激しいのも好きなの?
Wow.
うわ
Very big.
めっちゃびちょう
It's really shining.
めっちゃ光ってるよ
Ah, I think I'm going.
あー、いきそう
I can only drink it by mouth.
口だけに飲めちゃう
Ah, I think I'm going.
あー、いきそう
Did you remember that naughty feeling and made him the owner?
あのエッチなあと思い出しオーナーにした?
Yeah.
うん
Ah, I think I'm going.
あー、いきそう
Hmm.
うーん
ah.
あー
My legs were loose.
ぎゅっと足が抜けてました
I'll sleep properly.
ちゃんと寝るじゃん
ah,
あー、
I think I'll go.
い けそう
Try holding my knee.
僕の膝の方を持ってみて
Let's push a little closer.
ちょっと押し寄そう
Ah, amazing.
あー、すごい
Ah, that's amazing.
あー、すごいな
I want to try and attack it a little bit.
ちょっと頑張って攻めてみたいな
how was it?
どうだった?
Yeah, good.
うん、よかった